[
    {
      "id": "1",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "How fast can the fastest land animal, the cheetah, go?",
      "answer": "75 mph",
      "choices": ["55 mph", "30 mph", "90 mph", "75 mph" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "2",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "What is the largest land animal?",
      "answer": "African Elephant",
      "choices": ["African Elephant", "Blue Whale", "Hippo", "Giraffe" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "3",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which of the following animals has the shortest lifespan?",
      "answer": "Chameleons",
      "choices": ["Pigeons", "Dogs", "Chameleons", "Tortoises" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "4",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which of the following animals usually DO NOT travel in groups?",
      "answer": "Tigers",
      "choices": ["Tigers", "Dolphins", "Orcas", "Lions" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "5",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which of the following snakes are venomous?",
      "answer": "Cobras",
      "choices": ["Pythons", "Kingsnakes", "Boas", "Cobras" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "6",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which of these pairs of animals are not in a mutual relationship?",
      "answer": "Cuckoo Finch and Cisticola",
      "choices": ["Honey Badgers and Honeyguide Birds", "Sharks and Cleaner Fish", "Crocodiles and Plover Birds", "Cuckoo Finch and Cisticola" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "7",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which of these places has the worldâ€™s largest biodiversity?",
      "answer": "The Amazon Rainforest",
      "choices": ["The African Savannah", "The Great Coral Reef", "Madagascar", "The Amazon Rainforest" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "8",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which animal has the strongest jaw strength?",
      "answer": "Crocodiles",
      "choices": ["Gorillas", "Hippos", "Crocodiles", "Grizzly Bears" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "9",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which animal has the largest eyes?",
      "answer": "Giant Squids",
      "choices": ["Tarsiers", "Owls", "Giant Squids", "Slow Loris" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "10",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which of the following sea animal is NOT an actual animal?",
      "answer": "Hard Knucklefish",
      "choices": ["Lumpsucker", "Wunderpus photogenicus", "Dumbo Octopus", "Hard Knucklefish" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "11",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which bird has the largest wingspan?",
      "answer": "Wandering Albatross",
      "choices": ["Andean Condor", "Trumpeter Swan", "Wandering Albatross", "Great White Pelican" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "12",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which of the following animals are able to utilize echolocation?",
      "answer": "Shrews",
      "choices": ["Hummingbirds", "Flying Fish", "Cicadas", "Shrews" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "13",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which of the following inventions took inspiration from Kingfishers?",
      "answer": "Bullet Trains",
      "choices": ["Airplanes", "Bullet Trains", "Space Telescopes", "Cargo Trucks" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "14",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which animal is strictly a carnivore?",
      "answer": "Walruses",
      "choices": ["Sea Turtles", "Grizzly Bears", "Hummingbirds", "Walruses" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "15",
      "category" : "animals",
      "question": "Which of the following aquatic animals lay their eggs in shallow waters?",
      "answer": "Salmon",
      "choices": ["Deep-sea Skates", "Dolphins", "Octopus", "Salmon" ]
    },

    {
      "id": "1",
      "category": "science",
      "question": "Which of the following scientists created the AC motor?",
      "answer": "Nikola Tesla",
      "choices": ["Thomas Edison", "Nikola Tesla", "Alva J. Fisher", "Isaac Newton"]
    }

]